<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<chapters>
    <chapter chapterID="0">
        <text>
Restart?
        </text>

        <option resultID="0">Yes, restart, please</option>
        <option resultID="1">No, please, stop it</option>

        <result nextChapterID="0">Restarting from checkpoint...</result>
        <!--to end of the game-->
        <result nextChapterID="69">Bad for you:(</result>
    </chapter>

    <chapter chapterID="1">
        <text>
    CHAPTER 1
---------------
    3108 year. World of full science progress.
    Scientist Mad came into a room where was a girl.
- Betty, i didn't get final drug element for your incurable modern for 3108 year disease. There was no S.A.L.O. in Museum of Ancient Stuff... But i grabbed the Vishivanka.
- What happened with you? Why you are covered in blood? - she said quietly.

    Tell her...
        </text>

        <option resultID="0">... full museum story.</option>
        <option resultID="1">... nothing.</option>

        <result nextChapterID="2">
    OK then. Flashback to museum.</result>
        <result nextChapterID="4">- We have no time, Betty, you're dying, so forget...</result>
    </chapter>

    <chapter chapterID="2" isFight="true" isRestart="true">
        <text>
    69 minutes flashbackward.

    Mad sneaked into museum from backdoor, stealthed between robo-guards and finally maneged to Hall of 21 century Ukraine. Sadly, he could not find S.A.L.O., and robo-guard found Him.
    After robot shocked scientist... with a shocker, fight began.

to see full characters stats type or press: /charactersStats
        </text>

    </chapter>

    <chapter chapterID="3">
        <text>
    Robots surrounded scientist.
    After knockdown, scientist stood up, took first what he could, it was the Vishivanka, and his last chance was to run to the window.

    He will run ...
        </text>

        <option resultID="0">Zig-zag style</option>
        <option resultID="1">Straight forward</option>

        <result nextChapterID="4">    Robo-guards shot askew, and scientist could escape and run home.</result>
        <result nextChapterID="0">    Robo-guards triangulated his way and shot ahead. After first shot in his side, scientist fell down. Robots surrounded him and last thing he could think about was:
    "I wish i've ran zigzag style."
    Good news: his Creator allows this.
        </result>
    </chapter>

    <chapter chapterID="4">
        <text>
-... but its ok, i will time travel and whatever it takes get S.A.L.O.. Is our time travel machine still somewhere in the garage?
- Yes, it is in a garage, but how the Vishivanka will help ypu with that?
- No time to explain, you already ask stupido questions. Of course i'll put it in time travel machine in a position where it will find out time and place and take me there in 5 secs. Ez. If everything is ok, i will enter this room in 2 minutes.
    Scientist ran to the garage, where found time machine, put there the Vishivanka, which was in his blood.
    But bad for him he didn't see the bat witch lives in that machine's time and place decider.
    Any way he entered the machine and the only thing left was to press ready!
        </text>

        <option resultID="0">Ready!</option>

        <result nextChapterID="5">- I'm coming, 21 century Ukraine!</result>
    </chapter>

    <chapter  chapterID="5">
        <text>
    ....time traveling pew pew....
    Time machine sad:
- Welcome to the Transilvania world!

    CHAPTER 2
---------------
    To be continued...
        </text>

        <option resultID="0">oykey:(</option>

        <result nextChapterID="69">q</result>
    </chapter>


    <chapter chapterID="69">
        <text>This is the end.
        </text>
        <option resultID="0">Characters story list?</option>
        <option resultID="1">I will never play this game anymore.</option>

        <result nextChapterID="0">Loading character list...</result>
        <result nextChapterID="4">Suck it, noob, play minecraft.</result>
    </chapter>

</chapters>
