<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<chapters>
    <chapter chapterID="0">
        <text>
Restart?
        </text>

        <option resultID="0">Yes, restart, please</option>
        <option resultID="1">No, please, stop it</option>

        <result nextChapterID="0">Restarting from checkpoint...</result>
        <!--to end of the game-->
        <result nextChapterID="69">Bad for you:(</result>
    </chapter>

    <chapter chapterID="1">
        <text>
    CHAPTER 1
---------------
    3108 year. World of full science progress but very high radiation level.
Scientist was working on his RotationToPast Machine in his basement. Next to him was his cat in a gas mask too. Doc began to talk to the cat.
- Hey, Jo, remind me, am i that crazy or animals evolved and really can speak?
- Eh, yeah, but not all of us, only human's pets and ones who could survive radiation storms. Not everyone got lucky to have a master who made them a gas mask and a breathing device. - sad the cat with an accent similar to Great Britain English.
- Don't applaud me. - said Doc with a pride.
- Even if i could, i wouldn't. What take you so long, damn, when you will finish this thing? World won't save itself!
- Dude, if i finish it, time won't matter.
- True, but im not immortal...
After a few moments Doc asked the cat:
- Hey, You, could you pass me .., wait whaat? how did you fell asleep that fast?
- Its typical cat feature. What do you need?
        </text>

        <option resultID="0" karma="1">Pet the Cat</option>
        <option resultID="1" karma="-1">Push the Cat</option>

        <result nextChapterID="2">
*cat purred*
Now Doc could friendly ask him.</result>
        <result nextChapterID="3">
- Why would you do this? - cat now is pissed off.
*cat hissed(shhhh)*
Better not to annoy him.</result>
    </chapter>

    <chapter chapterID="2">
        <text>
- Cat! Pass me...
        </text>

        <option resultID="0" canBeInactive="true">Screwdriver</option>
        <option resultID="1" canBeInactive="true">Sandwich flavored pasta</option>
        <option resultID="2">Atomic battery</option>
        <option resultID="3" canBeInactive="true">Your mom</option>

        <result nextChapterID="2" >
- Here you go!- said the cat and with some pushes with its paws screwdriver got to its final destination.
- Thanks, my Pussy!
- Wow wow wow, don't say that! C'mon!</result>
        <result nextChapterID="2">
- One Sandwich flavored pasta for you and one tuna flavored pasta for me!
        </result>
        <result nextChapterID="4">
- Wait, we don't have any, last battery you took was that one you used to blow up some mutants for fun. I told you not to waste it!</result>
        <result nextChapterID="2">
- Realy? That was literally funny thousand years ago!
        </result>
    </chapter>

    <chapter chapterID="3">
        <text>
- Cat! Pass me...
        </text>

        <option resultID="0" canBeInactive="true">Screwdriver</option>
        <option resultID="1" canBeInactive="true">Sandwich flavored pasta</option>
        <option resultID="2">Atomic battery</option>
        <option resultID="3" canBeInactive="true">Your mom</option>

        <result nextChapterID="2" >
- Aha, sure. Take it by yourself. - replied Cat.
- You are mad or what? Any way, i don't need it.</result>
        <result nextChapterID="2">
Cat took that pasta tube and began fast to squeeze it out and eat it.
- Sorry, but it was last Sandwich flavored pasta. - Cat mocked Doc and evil laughed.
- You are a Monster.</result>
        <result nextChapterID="4">
- Doc, i'm tired to remind you: you wasted it to blow up mutants. FOR FUN. It was so bad idea, now they hate you more then even i do now.</result>
        <result nextChapterID="2">
- WTF. Do you to fight again? Last time we fought you fell in coma for 2 days. So better stop it.</result>
    </chapter>

    <chapter chapterID="4">
        <text>
Robots surrounded scientist.
After knockdown, scientist stood up, took first what he could, it was the Vishivanka, and his last chance was to run to the window.

He will run ...
        </text>

        <option resultID="0" karma="1">Zig-zag style</option>
        <option resultID="1" karma="-1" canBeInactive="true">Straight forward</option>

        <result nextChapterID="4">Robo-guards shot askew, and scientist could escape and run home.</result>
        <result nextChapterID="0">Robo-guards triangulated his way and shot ahead. After first shot in his side, scientist fell down. Robots surrounded him and last thing he could think about was:
"I wish i've ran zigzag style."
Good news: his Creator allows this.
        </result>
    </chapter>

    <chapter chapterID="5">
        <text>
-... but its ok, i will time travel and whatever it takes get S.A.L.O.. Is our time travel machine still somewhere in the garage?
- Yes, it is in a garage, but how the Vishivanka will help ypu with that?
- No time to explain, you already ask stupido questions. Of course i'll put it in time travel machine in a position where it will find out time and place and take me there in 5 secs. Ez. If everything is ok, i will enter this room in 2 minutes.
Scientist ran to the garage, where found time machine, put there the Vishivanka, which was in his blood.
But bad for him he didn't see the bat witch lives in that machine's time and place decider.
Any way he entered the machine and the only thing left was to press ready!
        </text>

        <option resultID="0" karma="1">Ready!</option>

        <result nextChapterID="5">- I'm coming, 21 century Ukraine!</result>
    </chapter>

    <chapter  chapterID="6">
        <text>
....time traveling pew pew....
Time machine sad:
- Welcome to the Transilvania world!

    CHAPTER 2
---------------
To be continued...
        </text>

        <option resultID="0">oykey:(</option>

        <result nextChapterID="69">q</result>
    </chapter>


    <chapter chapterID="69">
        <text>
This is the end.
        </text>
        <option resultID="0">Characters story list?</option>
        <option resultID="1">I will never play this game anymore.</option>

        <result nextChapterID="0">Loading character list...</result>
        <result nextChapterID="4">Suck it, noob, play minecraft.</result>
    </chapter>

</chapters>
